[
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "question": "According to this notebook, what is the primary goal of a movie recommendation system?",
          "answer": "To recommend movies based on the review of previous movie",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              2
          ],
         "question": "What are the two main approaches to build recommendation system as per this notebook?",
            "answer": "Content-based recommenders and Collaborative filtering engines",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              1
          ],
           "question": "What is the purpose of a recommender system?",
          "answer": "To predict the \"rating\" or \"preference\" that a user would give to an item, and improve the quality of search results and provide more relevant items to a user.",
           "task":"Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
    {
          "cell_ids":[
              2
          ],
          "question":"What does a collaborative recommender use to suggest items?",
           "answer": "It uses item metadata, such as genre, director, description, actors, etc. for movies, to make recommendations.",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
      },
       {
          "cell_ids": [
              2
          ],
          "question": "What is the main principle behind collaborative filtering?",
            "answer": "To match persons with similar interests and provides recommendations based on this matching.",
            "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
      },
   {
          "cell_ids": [
             13
          ],
          "question": "What is TF-IDF and how is it used in this recommendation system?",
          "answer": "TF-IDF is a statistical method of evaluating the significance of a word in a given document. The TF-IDF vectorizer is used to convert the text in product description into numerical data for analysis.",
          "task": "Topic Modeling",
          "skill": "Latent Dirichlet Allocation"
     },
        {
           "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
           "question": "What is the use of dot product layer in a recommendation system model?",
           "answer":"To compute the dot product between the embeddings to merge them together.",
            "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
      },
       {
          "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
           "question": "What does  `Reshape` layer do in the neural network?",
          "answer":"It is a utility layer needed to correct the shape of the dot product",
          "task":"Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
      {
           "cell_ids":[
            16
            ],
             "question":"what is the effect of the `sigmoid` activation in the classification model?",
           "answer":"It squashes the outputs between 0 and 1 because the labels are either 0 or 1.",
              "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
         },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              17
          ],
           "question": "How is a movie and a user combined in Dot Product Model?",
           "answer": "By doing dot product between embedding vectors of user and movie",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill":"Matrix Factorization"
      }
  ]